<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creations on Sebastian Lubene</title>
    <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creations on Sebastian Lubene</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beer Servings</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/beer/</guid>
      <description>In this project we take a quick look at beer consumption over the word.
Python libraries used: Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Seaborn
Some queries in the project:
 Countries where it doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist informations about beer consumption Total beer consumed by countries that consumed less than 100 per servings Calculate the average, median, min and max of beer servings Find top 10 largest and smallest beer consuming countries  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid19 Data Cleansing</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/covid19/</guid>
      <description>This project consists in analysing data about cases, deaths, vaccinations on Covid-19 over the world.
We&amp;rsquo;ll look at:
 Total cases vs Total deaths Total cases vs population Countries with highest infection rate compare to population Countries with highest death count per population Total population vs vaccinations  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard - Adventure Work </title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/adventurework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/adventurework/</guid>
      <description>This project is about designing and delivering a professional-quality, end-to-end business intelligence solution using Microsoft Power BI.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be working through the entire business intelligence workflow:
 Connecting and shaping the source data Building a relational model Adding calculated columns and measures Designing an interactive report  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard - Covid-19</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/covid/</guid>
      <description>In this project I will be taking some of the SQL queries I worked in the SQL data exploration project Covid19 Data Cleansingand creating visualization in Tableau.
Create dashboard
 Total Deaths per continent Percent population infected ( actual and estimate) Percent population infected per country Global numbers (Total cases, deaths, and death percentage)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard - Maven Market</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/mavenmarket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/mavenmarket/</guid>
      <description>This project is about designing and delivering a professional-quality, end-to-end business intelligence solution using Microsoft Power BI.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be working through the entire business intelligence workflow:
 Connecting and shaping the source data Building a relational model Adding calculated columns and measures Designing an interactive report  If you want to access a certain Product Name by a specific Product Brand in Product dashboard, in Topline Performance dashboard right click on the Product Brand, select Drill through and Product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demographic data</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/demographic_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/demographic_data/</guid>
      <description>For this project I used Python libraries: Pandas and Numpy
This project consists in analyzing a dataset of demographic data that was extracted from the 1994 Census database.\
To do that, I&amp;rsquo;ll be answering the following questions:
  How many people of each race are represented in this dataset?
  What is the average age of men?
  What is the percentage of people who have a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Correlation</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/movie-correlation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/movie-correlation/</guid>
      <description>In this project we look at what variables effect the gross revenue from movies.
Python libraries used: Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Seaborn
Steps:
 Import Python libraries Read in Data using Pandas Check for missing data Data cleaning Find correlations in the data  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Salaries</title>
      <link>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lubene.dev/projects/creations/schools/</guid>
      <description>This project consists in analysing data about salaries of different type of schools (Engineering, Ivies, Liberal Arts, State).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>